<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Programming on River Ranz</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/programming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Programming on River Ranz</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 20:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/programming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BreakaBull</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/breakabull/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/breakabull/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ever heard the phrase &amp;ldquo;bull in a china shop?&amp;rdquo; These five words were the inspiration behind &lt;em&gt;BreakaBull&lt;/em&gt;, a VR game where you play as a bull running a tea shop.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[INSERT BULL]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-breakabull&#34;&gt;Why BreakaBull?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;BreakaBull&lt;/em&gt; is a cozy game, but it also has a unique level of difficulty to it. Since you play as a bull, you have to do everything with your hooves. This can range from making tea and serving customers to sweeping and doing soothing chores around the tea shop. Seems simple enough, right? But the difficulty lies with the hooves— without the luxury of opposable thumbs, every task requires careful consideration and grace. Gameplay is focused on navigating a world that isn&amp;rsquo;t built for you, but without any stressful stakes. Do your best to appease the clientele— or don&amp;rsquo;t. We won&amp;rsquo;t tell.&#xA;Every day, customers will come into the tea shop. They&amp;rsquo;re unique, too— each customer has their own backstory and will talk to you about their day, their past, their hopes and dreams&amp;hellip; every one of them is their own &lt;del&gt;person&lt;/del&gt; animal.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heart of the Cards</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/heartofthecards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/heartofthecards/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Heart of the Cards&lt;/em&gt; was born from the intersection of dating sims and deckbuilders. For this 3-month project, our team worked to bring the idea to life. Unfortunately, things fell through, and in the end, the project ended up feeling incomplete.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[INSERT KETCHUP RESPONSE]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-intention&#34;&gt;Our Intention&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We wanted to create something that hadn&amp;rsquo;t been done before. The team was heavy on narrative specialists, and so we absolutely needed to have fun characters and an interesting story. Our game idea was formed fairly quickly, and the team was excited about the prospect of &lt;em&gt;Heart of the Cards&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nest Quest</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/nestquest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/nestquest/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If there&amp;rsquo;s one thing the &lt;em&gt;Nest Quest&lt;/em&gt; team loved, it was ducks. We knew from the start that our game needed to involve them in some way, and it didn&amp;rsquo;t take long after that for our concept to come together. We decided to aim for something both children and adults could enjoy, with bright colors, cute sounds, and adorable mechanics. And with that, &lt;em&gt;Nest Quest&lt;/em&gt; was born.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[INSERT NEST]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-role&#34;&gt;My Role&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As one of two programmers for &lt;em&gt;Nest Quest&lt;/em&gt;, I worked on a number of mechanics for the game. I implemented design ideas, tested them, and fixed bugs as they arose. We only had 3 months to complete this project, and thus it was important to focus on functionality and appearances to give the illusion of what the player expects.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
